

ABOUT ME

I am a beginner programmer with a deep interest in the Web. development. I have been studying programming for 1.5 years. I have basic knowledge in languages PHP(OOP), MySQL as well as experience in developing web applications on Laravel framework using JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap. Wrote several Pet-projects, with examples you can look at GitHub. Completed courses on the basics of algorithms and data structures and design patterns. Actively adhere to the standards for writing PSR code. I am sure that my motivation and desire to learn new will allow me to successfully achieve my professional goals and achieve success in a career as a programmer

LINKS

Portfolio:

https://pshenychnyi-portfolio.verc el.app/

GitHub:

https://github.com/Pshnychnyi

https://www.instagram.com/pshen ychnyi artem/

ARTFM PSHENYCHNYI

WER DEVELOPMENT



WORK EXPERIENCE

ARTEM **PSHENYCHNYI**

Oct 2022 - Nov 2023

WEB DEVELOPMENT

My first Pet-project - Corporate site. Written in the Laravel framework. It has administrative and user part with using a MySQL database. is elements used to highlight the active item menu, send an asynchronous request to the server, and form processing. Git repository: https://github.com/Pshnychnyi/it.loc

ARTEM **PSHENYCHNYI** Jan 2023 - Mar 2023

WEB DEVELOPMENT

The second project is an online fruit store. Written in the Laravel framework using MvSQL databases. The site consists of user part and administrative panels. For custom form processing parts and adding / removing goods to / from the basket asynchronous requests are used. On the site there is a full-fledged basket, and there is also comment block. Git repository: https://github.com/Pshnychnyi/fruitshop.loc

ARTEM PSHENYCHNYI

Nov 2022 - Dec 2023

WEB DEVELOPMENT

Mini CRM system. Written in the Vue framework 3. In this project, I used such tools like Vue-cli, Vue-router, Vuex as well Materialize elements. authentication system and registration implemented using the database Firebase Git repository:

https://github.com/Pshnychnyi/mini_crm_system

EDUCATION

7ΔΤΚ

Zhytomyr 2016

NUBIP

Kiev 2020 Some College (no degree)

Bachelor

SKILLS

PHP LARAVEL

HTML/CSS MYSOL

JAVASCRIPT VUEJS

GIT